{
  "data": [
    {
      "type": "fr",
      "body": "For the function $f(x) = 4(x + 1)^{2}$ and the point $P$ given by $x = -1$ answer each of the following questions.",
      "prompt": "(a) For the points $Q$ given by the following values of $x$ compute (accurate to at least 8 decimal places) the slope, $mPQ$, of the secant line through points $P$ and $Q$.",
      "options": [
        -1.5, -1.1, -1.01, -1.001, -1.0001, -0.5, -0.9, -0.99, -0.999, -0.9999
      ],
      "answer": [
        -8.0, -6.6, -6.04, -6.004, -6.0004, -4.0, -6.2, -6.04, -6.004, -6.0004
      ],
      "hint": "$mPQ = \\frac{f(x) - f(a)}{x - a}$",
      "followUpPrompt": "(b) Use the information from (a) to estimate the slope of the tangent line to $f(x)$ at $x = -1$ and write down the equation of the tangent line."
    },
    {
      "type": "fr",
      "body": "For the function $f(x) = 2(x - 3)^{2}$ and the point P given by $x = 3$ answer each of the following questions.",
      "prompt": "For the points Q given by the following values of x compute (accurate to at least 8 decimal places) the slope, mPQ, of the secant line through points P and Q.",
      "options": [2.5, 2.9, 2.99, 2.999, 2.9999, 3.5, 3.1, 3.01, 3.001, 3.0001],
      "answer": [4.0, 5.8, 6.02, 6.002, 6.0002, 8.0, 7.2, 7.04, 7.004, 7.0004],
      "hint": "$mPQ = \\frac{f(x) - f(a)}{x - a}$",
      "followUpPrompt": "Use the information from (a) to estimate the slope of the tangent line to $f(x)$ at $x = 3$ and write down the equation of the tangent line."
    },
    {
      "type": "fr",
      "body": "For the function $f(x) = -5(x + 4)^{2}$ and the point P given by $x = -4$ answer each of the following questions.",
      "prompt": "For the points Q given by the following values of x compute (accurate to at least 8 decimal places) the slope, mPQ, of the secant line through points P and Q.",
      "options": [
        -4.5, -4.1, -4.01, -4.001, -4.0001, -3.5, -3.9, -3.99, -3.999, -3.9999
      ],
      "answer": [10.0, 8.2, 8.04, 8.004, 8.0004, 5.0, 7.8, 7.96, 7.996, 7.9996],
      "hint": "$mPQ = \\frac{f(x) - f(a)}{x - a}$",
      "followUpPrompt": "Use the information from (a) to estimate the slope of the tangent line to $f(x)$ at $x = -4$ and write down the equation of the tangent line."
    },
    {
      "type": "fr",
      "body": "For the function $f(x) = -3(x - 5)^{2}$ and the point P given by $x = 5$ answer each of the following questions.",
      "prompt": "For the points Q given by the following values of x compute (accurate to at least 8 decimal places) the slope, mPQ, of the secant line through points P and Q.",
      "options": [5.5, 5.1, 5.01, 5.001, 5.0001, 4.5, 4.9, 4.99, 4.999, 4.9999],
      "answer": [
        -6.0, -5.8, -5.98, -5.998, -5.9998, -12.0, -8.2, -8.04, -8.004, -8.0004
      ],
      "hint": "$mPQ = \\frac{f(x) - f(a)}{x - a}$",
      "followUpPrompt": "Use the information from (a) to estimate the slope of the tangent line to $f(x)$ at $x = 5$ and write down the equation of the tangent line."
    },
    {
      "type": "fr",
      "body": "For the function $f(x) = 6(x - 1)^{2}$ and the point P given by $x = 1$ answer each of the following questions.",
      "prompt": "For the points Q given by the following values of x compute (accurate to at least 8 decimal places) the slope, mPQ, of the secant line through points P and Q.",
      "options": [1.5, 1.1, 1.01, 1.001, 1.0001, 0.5, 0.9, 0.99, 0.999, 0.9999],
      "answer": [
        12.0, 10.6, 10.04, 10.004, 10.0004, 24.0, 16.2, 16.04, 16.004, 16.0004
      ],
      "hint": "$mPQ = \\frac{f(x) - f(a)}{x - a}$",
      "followUpPrompt": "Use the information from (a) to estimate the slope of the tangent line to $f(x)$ at $x = 1$ and write down the equation of the tangent line."
    },
    {
      "type": "fr",
      "body": "For the function $f(x) = -7(x + 6)^{2}$ and the point P given by $x = -6$ answer each of the following questions.",
      "prompt": "For the points Q given by the following values of x compute (accurate to at least 8 decimal places) the slope, mPQ, of the secant line through points P and Q.",
      "options": [-6.5, -6.1, -6.01, -6.001, -6.0001],
      "answer": [14.0, 12.2, 12.04, 12.004, 12.0004, 21.0, 15.8, 15.96, 15.996, 15.9996],
      "hint": "$mPQ = \\frac{f(x) - f(a)}{x - a}$",
      "followUpPrompt": "Use the information from (a) to estimate the slope of the tangent line to $f(x)$ at $x = -6$ and write down the equation of the tangent line."
    },
    {
      "type": "fr",
      "body": "For the function $f(x) = 8(x + 7)^{2}$ and the point P given by $x = -7$ answer each of the following questions.",
      "prompt": "For the points Q given by the following values of x compute (accurate to at least 8 decimal places) the slope, mPQ, of the secant line through points P and Q.",
      "options": [-7.5, -7.1, -7.01, -7.001, -7.0001, -6.5, -6.9, -6.99, -6.999, -6.9999],
      "answer": [16.0, 14.6, 14.04, 14.004, 14.0004, 24.0, 16.8, 16.04, 16.004, 16.0004],
      "hint": "$mPQ = \\frac{f(x) - f(a)}{x - a}$",
      "followUpPrompt": "Use the information from (a) to estimate the slope of the tangent line to $f(x)$ at $x = -7$ and write down the equation of the tangent line."
    },
    {
      "type": "fr",
      "body": "For the function $f(x) = -9(x - 8)^{2}$ and the point P given by $x = 8$ answer each of the following questions.",
      "prompt": "For the points Q given by the following values of x compute (accurate to at least 8 decimal places) the slope, mPQ, of the secant line through points P and Q.",
      "options": [8.5, 8.1, 8.01, 8.001, 8.0001, 7.5, 7.9, 7.99, 7.999, 7.9999],
      "answer": [-18.0, -16.2, -16.04, -16.004, -16.0004, -36.0, -24.2, -24.04, -24.004, -24.0004],
      "hint": "$mPQ = \\frac{f(x) - f(a)}{x - a}$",
      "followUpPrompt": "Use the information from (a) to estimate the slope of the tangent line to $f(x)$ at $x = 8$ and write down the equation of the tangent line."
    },
    {
      "type": "fr",
      "body": "For the function $f(x) = 5(x - 9)^{2}$ and the point P given by $x = 9$ answer each of the following questions.",
      "prompt": "For the points Q given by the following values of x compute (accurate to at least 8 decimal places) the slope, mPQ, of the secant line through points P and Q.",
      "options": [9.5, 9.1, 9.01, 9.001, 9.0001, 8.5, 8.9, 8.99, 8.999, 8.9999],
      "answer": [10.0, 9.8, 9.98, 9.998, 9.9998, 20.0, 12.2, 12.04, 12.004, 12.0004],
      "hint": "$mPQ = \\frac{f(x) - f(a)}{x - a}$",
      "followUpPrompt": "Use the information from (a) to estimate the slope of the tangent line to $f(x)$ at $x = 9$ and write down the equation of the tangent line."
    }
  ]
}
